We mentioned this several times. Put the SW in
the resource folder name stands for smallest width. To drive
home that point, let's walk through a hypothetical situation. Say
you have an app directory structure like this. We have
some layouts defined in the base layout folder and
we override some of those in the layout-sw600dp folder. We
also override one of these in the layout-sw720dp folder. Let's
look at which layouts would be applied on which device.
Say your app is running on a Nexxus five.
The Nexxus five has dimensions 360 dp by six 640
dp. Of the two, the smallest width is 360 dp.
So we use this number to compare it against the
folder names. 360 dp is less than 600 and
is less than, 720 so all the layouts will come
from the space layout folder. For the Nexus 72012 version,
the dimensions are 600 dp by 960 dp. Of the
two sides 600 dp is the smaller width. So you compare
this against the folder names. It turns out that the smallest width
is greater than or equal to 600 dp, so for the
detail and the item layout, we pull it from this folder. Now
the main .xml file is not declared in this folder, so
we fall back to a less specific folder, which turns out to
be this one in the base layout folder. For the Nexus ten,
the dimensions are 800 dp by 1280 dp. Of the two sides,
800 dp is the smallest width. Now this device satisfies
the categories for all of these because 800 is greater than
720 and greater than 600. However, the system chooses the
most specific folder first. So it will choose this item layout
over these two. Since the detail layout is not defined
here, it will fall back to a less specific folder, which
is this one. Then for the main.xml file, it's not declared
in either of these, so it falls back to this one.